txrestaurant.org 2017-09-15

# Privacy Policy | Texas Restaurant Association

Your privacy is our primary concern.

TRAmarketplace.com makes every effort to provide you with a safe and private environment. TRAmarketplace.com’s privacy policy tells you what information we gather and how we use it. This privacy policy applies to all of the Texas Restaurant Association (TRA) sites.

Information collection

TRAmarketplace.com collects two types of information:

Personal information

When you sign up for services, you may be asked to provide personal information. Personal data may also be requested when registering for seminars or e-mail services. This information will not be released without authorization from you and we will not disclose personal identification information.

Web site activity data

Activity data is gathered through several methods and is tracked as a whole rather than individually. This allows us to track the tramarketplace.com Web site—we never use it to personally identify you. By tracking, we can build the most effective Web site for all visitors. Generally, we look at how well pages, products or sections of the Web site perform based on traffic. Specifically, we can determine which areas are most effective or appropriate based on the amount of traffic to particular areas.

Information usage

TRAmarketplace.com will not disclose any business or personal information that identifies you to any third party without your consent unless we clearly define the nature and manner of disclosure or disclosure is legally required or to protect our rights. If you unsubscribe from any of our e-mails, your name will be shared with all list vendors whom we purchase lists from so that your e-mail address will be included on that do-not-e-mail list as well.

Cookies and tracking

As you browse TRA's websites, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with us. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number. You can [visit this page to opt out](https://app.adroll.com/optout/safari) of AdRoll’s and their partners’ targeted advertising.

Web sites will commonly write small data files (cookies) to your hard drive during your visits to the site. A cookie file is used in order to track your traffic patterns on a particular site and contains information that can anonymously identify you. This information is encrypted for security purposes. Restaurantville.com measures the activity of the site by using cookies. Cookies help us make improvements to the site so that you can have a pleasant and productive experience. Cookies are created to identify your computer when visiting our site and are never used to identify you personally. Cookies can't read data off of your hard disk, do damage to your hard disk or memory or read cookie files created by other sites. You can set your browser to send a warning message before accepting cookies or to refuse cookies. Check with your browser for instructions on how to handle cookies.

Notification of privacy changes

TRAmarketplace.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. When changes are made, they will be posted to the Web site immediately.

E-Commerce areas and partner sites

Information requested by the TRA and its Web sites is provided and approved by you. Information requested by other firms, organizations, linked Web sites and partner sites reached through any TRA Web site but not controlled by the TRA for purchases is provided on a voluntary basis by you. Affiliate online merchants have privacy and data collection practices of their own. Please consult the partner's home page for the company profile, which will detail their practices. The TRA (as well as any TRA Web sites) DO NOT HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE PRACTICES OF FIRMS, WEB SITES AND/OR PARTNER SITES NOT OWNED BY THE TRA.

Credit card data

TRAmarketplace.com recognizes your concerns about Web commerce and transactions using bank and credit card information. PayPal is our credit card processor so if you paid using a credit card, you will get a payment confirmation e-mail from PayPal. Learn more about PayPal’s security [here](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/paypal-safety-and-security).

DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

The content provided on this website is provided as a service to TRA members and the public. Information presented on this website is provided for informational purposes only. No information presented on this website constitutes legal advice, nor does it create an attorney-client relationship between TRA and any other party.

You acknowledge and agree that this site and the content therein are provided on an "as is" and "as available" basis.

Neither TRA nor any of its affiliates warrants that this site will be uninterrupted or error free or that this site, its server or any files available for downloading through this sites are free of computer viruses or other harmful elements. You expressly agree that the entire risk as to the quality and performance of this site and the accuracy or completeness of the content is assumed solely by you.

TRA does not make any, and hereby specifically disclaims any, representations, endorsements, guarantees, or warranties, express or implied, regarding this site or any content, including without limitation, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose and non-infringement of third-party rights. Without limiting the foregoing, TRA disclaims any warranties with respect to any results that may be obtained from the use of this site.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

Under no circumstances will TRA be liable for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained through the content on the web site. It is your responsibility to evaluate the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information or any content available through the web site.
